The unknown entity which appeared without warning in Tokyo airspace
has yet to show signs of activity.
Discontent towards the government is building among the citizens,
who are confined to evacuation shelters.
For the—
For the first time since the war, the JSDF has been mobilized as part of a public security operation.
How this will affect—
...will affect international relations is uncertain.
Heavenly Arbiter
Just now, we've received an update.
Mysterious Entity in Air On Tokyo Airspace Is Moving
It appears the object has begun to move.
Allow me to repeat:
Mysterious Entity in Air On Tokyo Airspace Is Moving
... we've received an update.
It appears the object has begun to move.
Allow me to repeat:
The target is maintaining its trajectory.
[something] in response to contact
We're on red alert here.
Can't you hear the alarms?
No, I can hear.
It's just...
I was going to call everyone.
It's a big one, all right.
Must be around three hundred meters.
The target's energy readings are rising.
Funagai, reporting for duty.
What took you?
Looks like it's tired of waiting.
Are we ready for contact?
We're ready.
Good.
We've received an emergency summons, Midori.
I was getting sick of waiting.
Here I come!
You're so aggressive, Misaki.
You're one to talk!
Try this on for size!
Now look what you've done—
it's covered in mud!
What's the matter, Rin?
Oh, right—we're being summoned.
Finally time for action, is it?
Misaki, look.
Are you planning to stay in there forever?
What?
Well, don't just stand there.
I'm going on ahead.
Five whole years already, huh?
All agents have arrived.
Your objective is to annihilate the target.
Take it out whatever the cost.
Destroy the enemy.
We'll have the JSDF act as bait.
With its massive power,
it can't fire again straight away
after releasing energy.
It needs time to recharge.
That's the enemy?
Listen up.
Failure is not an option.
It's in your hands now, Funagai.
There are two steps required to neutralize our opponent.
We have to discover its weakness and then destroy it.
We'll fire a probe at close range with a bazooka,
analyze the controlling core
and focus our fire to destroy it.
W-With a bazooka?
Once its energy readings drop,
you will move out and engage.
Strike swiftly and retreat.
Consider this the only chance we've got.
Rin Ichikawa.
Y-Yes?
You'll take point.
Strike the core.
Understood.
Captain!
The JSDF has engaged the target.
The target's energy readings have passed the threshold.
I can't agree with this order, Captain.
Why am I backup?
You have a problem with my commands?
I do.
Rin, go on ahead.
Are you fine letting her go?
What's that supposed to mean?
I don't let personal feelings interfere with work!
Then make me take point!
I'm superior to Rin in all areas.
I can accomplish this task.
You act on your own authority.
You're a loose cannon.
So that's it.
I'm inferior to Rin, am I?
Misaki...
I'll show him.
I'll prove I'm superior to Rin.
Ensure you penetrate the target directly with the probe.
With this improvised weapon?
01 Skelter Wave, copy that.
Skelter Wave, preparing for launch.
Roger!
Misaki's completely right.
She'd do a better job for sure.
But I want to live up to Captain Funagai's expectations.
No one's going to listen to excuses.
I won't give in to the enemy or my own weakness.
Then I'll tell him how I feel!
Energy readings increasing.
All units, prepare to engage.
01 in pursuit.
03, cover me.
You got it.
Nicely done, Misaki.
We landed safely.
We can do this!
Readying probe!
Retreat as soon as you've planted it.
02, attack as soon as the scan's completed.
Roger!
Misaki!
Behind you!
Midori!
Ignore it! Focus on the target!
But Misaki...
And Midori!
Follow your orders!
Analysing.
Core detected in center of object.
The entity's exterior is heavily armored,
so enter from underneath.
Are you listening, Rin?
There's no time for emotions.
02 will provide cover fire.
Rin!
This is an artificial human.
As it grows, its intelligence will surpass a human's,
along with its physical abilities.
However, its true capabilities are unknown.
Strict supervision will be required.
It is currently docile.
But if one day it were to turn against us...
Captain, how long will I be able to live?
Are you afraid of dying?
Not at all.
It's just... I'm an artificial being.
My lifespan is different to yours.
So I...
I want to understand my own life.
The organisation is responsible for all of your wellbeing.
There's nothing to be worried about.
We won't know your lifespan without more research.
As the first generation,
you are the research subjects.
That's enough pointless chitchat.
You just need to follow orders.
All right?
Understood.
That's good.
Your orders are absolute.
You're as honest as they come, aren't you?
What's that?
Rin, focus!
I'm fine, I'm fine.
I can still fight!
Rin... no.
All units, retreat.
We'll fall back.
When we figure out its weakness, we'll attack together and destroy it!
Funagai! Have you gone insane?
I told myself it was just work.
I was able to convince myself it was professional.
But those girls
were smiling.
That's why... That's why...
Rin! What are you doing?
I didn't follow your orders all this time because of how I was created!
It was because I loved you!
That's right.
I'm going in first!
Don't!
Stop it!
I got through!
Here we go, Rin!
Skelter fighter unit Skelter Wave has penetrated the target.
What on earth...
What is this?
This is the controlling core.
It's speaking directly into my mind
Certainly, some humans are slaves to their emotions.
And their history is one of destruction, no end in sight.
But that's only one side of humanity.
We have to defeat you.
But it's not for humanity.
It's for the one person I want to protect!
That's why I'm fighting!
Yes, that's exactly right.
Understood.
They weren't defective themselves.
The problem is how humans used them.
It always is.
One Year After
Breaking news.
Multiple mysterious entities have appeared in Tokyo's airspace.
Mysterious Entity in Air On Tokyo Airspace Is Moving
A similar entity was destroyed
by the JSDF one year ago.