SkelterSubs presents...
In Collaboration with:
ButterFS    0x539     Kaleido      LCE
SMC-Subs   Obelix      Kantai       HRI
Chyuu       TSCamp    PAS         Sodra
We are on a trip,
Tozasareteku taiyou
searching for the covered sun
sagashi ni tabidatou
For the sake of finding the dream that is gone
Nakushita yume wo torimodosu tame
Translation: Melancholy; TLC: jymmy; ED: Lann, 0x539
AAAAAAAAAAAAA
SED: Nazaki, 0x539; TM: Kuzu, Luceo; KTM: Shinon
TS: Sodra, Shinon; KFX: Shinon
A power you can't see
Mienai chikara ni ima
is guiding us
michibikareru mama
AAAAAAAAAAAAA
and we aim for a far away goal
Haruka tooku no GOAL mezashite
Where should we go in this town we have not seen?
Mishiranu machi bokura wa
doko he ikeba ii n darou
Our beating chest won't be lost, it'll keep running!
Takanaru mune mayowazu
hashiri tsudzuketai (ah-i-a-i-a-i-a-i-a)
We challange you with our lives on the line. I CAN FLY
Inochi wo kakete idomu I can fly
There are no scary things at all.
kowai mono nante nai
The heart of nakedness and heart are trying to connect!
Hadaka no kokoro to kokoro de
tsunagatteitai yo
Light of hope! Kanji in the sky!
Kibou no hikari kanji in the sky
Flying higher than anyone can get to.
dare yori mo takaku tobe
Before our eyes opens a fate
Me no mae no unmei kirihirake owaru koto nai
to a future without an ending.
mirai he
Up to the sky