ayatsurareteku unmei ga
I leave my life up to fate. What can I do?
kanashimi no soko de kamawanai
Perhaps I live in deep despair, I don’t really care
tsunagareta ito anata e to tsuzuku
Here we are, it’s me and you. We’re tied by our two destinies
karami hodoite suki ni shite yo
But I know it might not be what you wish for in your
heart ugokasareteru hodo
Heart… The pain inside me grows much too strong
itami hashiru no
It makes me get up and fight
endless mezameru omoi ni
Endless… These feelings well up in my heart
kokyuu sae dekinai
I am crushed under all my feelings
anata wo mamoreru nara
What can I do to protect you? I cried
karada kuchihatete mo ii
I’d let myself break completely for you
ai no akashi wo daita
I have embraced all the love that’s inside
watashi wo mitete
Hey, why don’t you look my way?
mune ni te wo oshitsukete
Now lay your hand on this heart of my own
eien sagashiteru no
Let’s look for time everlasting, endless
itsumo hitori ni shinaide
I’m begging you please, don’t you leave me alone
watashi no subete wa sou
Life after won’t mean a thing, don’t you know?
anata kara hajimaru
All that I am is because of you