tozasareteku taiyou sagashi ni tabidatou
You'll always find us chasing in pursuit of a sun that's hiding away
nakushita yume wo torimodosu tame
'Cause there's a dream that we have lost and want to find again
mienai chikara ni ima michibikareru mama
There is a hidden power deep inside and it's always guiding our way
haruka tooku no gooru mezashite
Out in the distance, our goal is there to attain
mishiranu machi bokura wa
In a town that none of us really know,
doko e yukeba ii n darou
Where there's no one to show us which way we should go,
takanaru mune mayowazu
Know our hearts will never lead us astray
hashiri tsuzuketai (ah-i-a-i-a-i-a-i-a)
From the path that we should ta-a-ake!
inochi wo kakete idomu I can fly
Life on the line, I will spread my wings so I can fly!
kowai mono nante nai
'Cause why would I have anything to fear?
hadaka no kokoro to kokoro de
With my soul bared to your soul and your soul to mine,
tsunagatteitai yo
I want to fly out there with you
kibou no hikari kanji in the sky
Enter the light! We can fly high up in the sky
dare yori mo takaku tobe
With wings of hope, we're reaching new frontiers
me no mae no unmei kirihirake owaru koto nai mirai e
And now here right in front of our eyes stretching out to the skies, here our destiny lies for us to claim
up to the sky
Take to the sky!